[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Hey, can we get another
嘿，我们可以再买一个吗
Triple Gooberberry Sunrise
over here?
三重 Goobberry 日出
在这里？
And don't you skimp
on the triple.
你不要吝啬
在三重上。
Here's your sun...
这里是你的太阳...
It's starting!
开始了！
[laughs]
[笑]
I'll take another one.
我再拿一张。
This time with less manager.
这次经理较少。
Attention, children of all ages.
所有年龄段的孩子请注意。
- Hello, hi!
- Hey, that's me!
- 你好，你好！
- 嘿，这就是我！
- I love you, I love you!
- All ages, yay!
- 我爱你，我爱你！
- 所有年龄段，耶！
Put your fins together for
the cool cat on the drum kit,
将你的鳍放在一起
架子鼓上的酷猫，
Bongos Bear!
邦戈熊！
On trumpet, this bivalve
really swings.
在喇叭上，这种双壳类
真的很摇摆。
Clem Clam!
克莱姆 克莱姆！
You know him, you love him.
你认识他，你爱他。
Eight tentacles on 88 keys,
88个键上的8个触手，
it's Rock T. Puss.
我是洛克·T·普斯。
That's our combo.
这就是我们的组合。
Give it up
for the Goofy Scoopers!
放弃吧
为了高飞独家！
♪ A one and two and three
and four ♪
♪ 一、二、三
和四个♪
♪ I need more scoops,
ice cream galore ♪
♪ 我需要更多勺子，
冰淇淋满满的♪
♪ Or I'll banana split right
out that door ♪
♪ 或者我就吃香蕉船吧
走出那扇门♪
♪ Don't you know,
I'm doing the Goober Rag! ♪
♪ 你不知道吗，
我正在做古伯抹布！ ♪
[screams and cheers]
[尖叫声和欢呼声]
I love you, Rock T. Puss!
我爱你，Rock T. Puss！
♪ Oh, five and six and seven
and eight ♪
♪ 哦，五、六、七
和八个♪
♪ Finish my ice cream,
licking my plate ♪
♪ 吃完我的冰淇淋，
舔我的盘子♪
♪ Another fudge sundae
sure sounds great ♪
♪ 另一个软糖圣代
听起来确实很棒♪
♪ And that is how I do
that Goober Rag! ♪
♪ 我就是这么做的
那个古伯拉格！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪♪
♪ Nine and ten
and eleven and twelve ♪
♪ 九点和十点
还有十一和十二♪
♪ Get the Rum Raisin
off that shelf ♪
♪ 获取朗姆酒葡萄干
现货 ♪
♪ I'll eat the whole tub
all on my own ♪
♪ 我要把整个浴缸都吃掉
一切都靠我自己♪
♪ And I don't even need
a cone ♪
♪ 我什至不需要
一个圆锥体♪
♪ Don't you know, that's how ♪
♪ 你难道不知道吗 ♪
♪ Can't you see,
I'm doing it now ♪
♪ 你难道看不出来吗，
我现在就在做♪
♪ I'm coming, I'm going,
I'm doing the Goober Rag! ♪
♪ 我来了，我走了
我正在做古伯抹布！ ♪
[cheering]
[欢呼]
All right, boys, time to go.
好了，孩子们，该出发了。
You can't kick us out.
你不能把我们赶出去。
We've been coming here
since we were kids.
我们一直来这里
从我们小时候起。
Yeah, we're the
Goofy Scoopers' biggest fans.
是的，我们是
Goofy Scoopers 的最大粉丝。
Well, that's your problem.
好吧，那是你的问题。
Closing time.
关门时间。
[both crying]
[两人都哭了]
You don't have to go home,
你不必回家，
but you can't stay here.
但你不能留在这里。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
This stinks.
这很臭。
I wanted to go backstage
for an autograph.
我想去后台
索要签名。
Don't worry, Patrick.
别担心，帕特里克。
We'll just come back and see
the Goofy Scoopers tomorrow.
我们会回来看看
明天的高飞独家新闻。
[rooster crows]
[公鸡打鸣]
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Good morning.
- [screams]
- 早上好。
- [尖叫]
I don't carry cash!
我没带现金！
Huh? It's you two.
啊？是你们两个。
We camped out all night
to see the Gooey Sneakers.
我们整晚都在外面露营
去看Gooey运动鞋。
Goofy Scoopers.
高飞勺子。
Yeah, them!
是的，他们！
They're gonna write on my head.
他们会写在我头上。
Well...
出色地...
about that.
关于那个。
[mischievous music]
[恶作剧音乐]
Ee... yup.
呃...是的。
The Goofy Scoopers are over.
高飞独家新闻结束了。
Too old fashioned.
The kids want a new sound.
太老套了。
孩子们想要新的声音。
both: A new sound?
两人：新声音？
That's right, I brought in an
act you're going to flip over.
没错，我带了一个
表演你要翻身的动作。
Say hello to...
向...问好
DJ 2 Sc00pz!
DJ 2 Sc00pz！
[electronic music]
[电子音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Sorry, but the Goofy Scoopers
抱歉，高飞勺子
are the only ice cream themed
musical robot act
是唯一的冰淇淋主题
音乐机器人表演
we'll ever love.
我们会永远相爱。
[rhythmic grunting]
[有节奏的咕噜声]
Patrick, don't give in
帕特里克，别屈服
to its seductive
womp-womps and wub-wubs.
以其诱人的
womp-womps 和 wub-wubs。
Please, Mr. Manager,
经理先生，请
you have to tell us
where the Scoopers are.
你必须告诉我们
独家新闻在哪里。
Are they playing
at a coffee house?
他们在玩吗
在咖啡馆？
Are they playing
the Bikini Bottom Bowl?
他们在玩吗
比基尼底碗？
Or on a world tour?
还是去世界巡演？
Oh, my, no.
哦，天哪，不。
I threw those old robots
in the garbage.
我把那些旧机器人扔了
在垃圾中。
They're never playing anywhere again.
他们再也不会去任何地方玩了。
[both crying]
[两人都哭了]
All right, you're killing
the atmosphere in here.
好吧，你这是在杀人
这里的气氛。
Please do all your crying outside.
请在外面哭泣。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Wait a minute, Patrick.
等一下，帕特里克。
I have a plan.
我有一个计划。
We can stop crying.
我们可以停止哭泣。
Well, I wasn't crying.
还好我没有哭。
I was just...
我当时只是...
flushing my eyes.
红了我的眼睛。
You were saying?
你说的是？
We are gonna get the
Goofy Scoopers back together
我们将会得到
高飞勺子又聚在一起了
for a reunion show.
为了重聚表演。
Then everyone will remember
how great they were.
那么大家都会记住
他们多么伟大啊。
But we don't know
where they are.
但我们不知道
他们在哪里。
True, but we do know
how they got to where they were
确实如此，但我们确实知道
他们是如何到达目的地的
before they went
wherever they are.
在他们走之前
无论他们在哪里。
Hmm? Hmm? Ah.
唔？唔？啊。
I'm confused, but I
appreciate your confidence.
我很困惑，但我
感谢您的信心。
Count me in!
算我一个吧！
Ow.
噢。
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Huh.
呵呵。
[engine rumbles]
[发动机隆隆声]
[tires squealing]
Huh?
[轮胎吱吱声]
啊？
Sorry about borrowing
your truck!
借钱的事抱歉
你的卡车！
We have to save some robots
from the trash
我们必须拯救一些机器人
从垃圾中
so our favorite band
can get back together.
所以我们最喜欢的乐队
可以复合。
I'm sure you understand.
我相信你明白。
Eh, that sounds reasonable.
呃，听起来很有道理。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
Hey, what you boys doing
to my precious junk?
嘿，你们这些家伙在做什么
我珍贵的垃圾？
Sorry, sir.
对不起，先生。
I was just looking
for some robot musicians.
我只是在寻找
对于一些机器人音乐家来说。
And I was looking for food.
我正在寻找食物。
You gonna eat this hot dog?
你要吃这个热狗吗？
Well, I don't know nothing
about music-men,
嗯，我什么都不知道
关于音乐人，
but I do remember one robot
fella coming through here.
但我记得有一个机器人
有个人经过这里
Nice guy.
好人。
Sold him to the circus
for about $3.50.
把他卖给了马戏团
约 3.50 美元。
Patrick, it's our first clue.
帕特里克，这是我们的第一个线索。
We gotta get to the circus.
我们得去马戏团。
Great, 'cause I just found
the mayo.
太好了，因为我刚刚发现
蛋黄酱。
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Hey, what are you doing
in my precious junkyard?
嘿，你在做什么
在我珍贵的垃圾场里？
[lively music]
[活泼的音乐]
Patrick, it's Clem Clam.
帕特里克，我是克莱姆·克莱姆。
Let's get him.
我们来抓住他吧。
W-w-wait, Patrick.
等等，帕特里克。
We're here to make friends
with him, don't you remember?
我们来这里是为了交朋友
和他在一起，你不记得了吗？
Obviously, I do not.
显然，我不这么认为。
How are we gonna get him
to play the show?
我们怎样才能得到他
来表演？
I got it!
我得到了它！
We'll appeal to his intellect
我们将诉诸他的智慧
with sound reasoning
and convincing arguments.
有合理的推理
和令人信服的论据。
Please!
- We need you.
请！
- 我们需要你。
You gotta come back,
you just gotta.
你一定要回来，
你只需要。
You can cool it, cats.
你可以冷静下来，猫们。
Whatever your scheme is, I'm in.
不管你的计划是什么，我都参与。
Just get me out of this
crazy circus.
让我摆脱这一切
疯狂的马戏团。
I'm terrified of clowns, man.
我害怕小丑，伙计。
[honking]
[鸣喇叭]
[laughs]
[笑]
[shudders]
[颤抖]
Well, that's great,
Mr. Clem Clam,
嗯，那太好了，
克莱姆·克拉姆先生，
because tomorrow night, we're
getting the band back together.
因为明天晚上，我们
让乐队重聚。
Reunion show tomorrow night
at Goofy Goober's.
在高飞古伯家。
So far, you're the only one
we've found, though.
到目前为止，你是唯一的一个
不过我们已经发现了。
You know, the circus's
least flexible contortionist
你知道，马戏团的
最不灵活的柔术演员
saw Bongos Bear at that massage
place downtown, man.
在那次按摩中看到邦戈斯熊
地点在市中心，伙计。
It's true... ow...
确实是这样……呜呜……
Great, come on, Patrick.
太好了，来吧，帕特里克。
I feel another plan forming.
我感觉另一个计划正在形成。
- [laughs]
- Wait, take me with you, man.
- [笑]
- 等等，带我一起去吧，伙计。
Ahh!
- [snickers]
啊！
- [窃笑]
Ugh.
啊。
[relaxing music]
[轻松的音乐]
Uh, yes, my wife and I are
here for the couples massage.
呃，是的，我和我的妻子
这里是情侣按摩。
- [giggles]
- Say...
- [咯咯笑]
- 说...
aren't you Bongos Bear
from the Goofy Scoopers?
你不是邦戈熊吗
来自高飞勺子？
Son, you got the wrong
robot bear.
儿子，你错了
机器熊。
I don't even like music.
我什至不喜欢音乐。
I just give massages.
我只是做按摩。
Don't forget to work my glutes.
别忘了锻炼我的臀肌。
[shudders]
[颤抖]
[rhythmic grunts]
[有节奏的咕噜声]
[bongo sounds]
[邦戈声音]
All right, all right, you win.
好吧好吧，你赢了。
I am Bongos Bear.
我是邦戈斯熊。
And I got music in my cold,
robotic heart.
我在寒冷中听音乐，
机器人心脏。
both: Yay!
两人：耶！
Well, you're in luck,
'cause Patrick and I
嗯，你很幸运，
因为帕特里克和我
are getting your band
back together.
正在得到你的乐队
回到一起。
Yeah, but we still gotta find
the piano octopus.
是的，但我们还得找到
钢琴章鱼。
Oh, that's easy.
哦，这很容易。
A construction worker
with lumbago told me
一名建筑工人
腰痛告诉我
Rock is working on the bridge
to Shell City now.
岩石正在桥上工作
现在去贝壳城。
It's true... ow...
确实是这样……呜呜……
- Rock?
- Rock T. Puss?
- 岩石？
- 摇滚 T. 猫？
[panicked screams]
[惊慌的尖叫声]
This stinks.
这很臭。
Bongos lied.
I don't see him anywhere.
邦戈斯撒谎了。
我在任何地方都没有看到他。
- Hey!
- Get out of here.
- 嘿！
- 离开这里。
I'm on the job.
我正在工作。
Rock T. Puss,
摇滚 T. 猫，
we're SpongeBob and Patrick;
we're your biggest fans.
我们是海绵宝宝和帕特里克；
我们是你最大的粉丝。
Yeah, right.
是的，对。
No one remembers my music.
没有人记得我的音乐。
That's okay.
没关系。
I don't remember anything.
我什么都不记得了。
Look, kids,
I'm a working robot now.
看，孩子们，
我现在是一个工作机器人。
The only bands I care about
are the boats on this bridge.
我唯一关心的乐队
是这座桥上的船。
Their honking horns
他们的喇叭
are the only applause
I'll ever need again.
是唯一的掌声
我会再次需要。
[horn blares]
[喇叭声]
- Um...
- Oh, that was me.
- 嗯...
- 哦，那是我。
Sorry, I blame the hot dog.
抱歉，我责怪热狗。
Oh, please, Mr. Puss.
哦，拜托，猫先生。
We're getting the Goofy
Scoopers back together
我们遇到了高飞
舀回一起
for a reunion show.
为了重聚表演。
We need you.
我们需要你。
The answer is no.
答案是否定的。
I'm a bridge now.
Get out of here.
我现在是一座桥梁。
离开这里。
- [sighs]
- [whimpers]
- [叹气]
- [呜咽]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
Where's Rock?
洛克在哪里？
Oh, he's not coming.
哦，他不来了。
Wha?
世界卫生大会？
I don't know if we can do this
without Rock T. Puss.
我不知道我们是否可以做到这一点
没有Rock T. Puss。
Don't worry,
we'll be playing with you.
别担心，
我们会和你一起玩。
It'll be fun.
会很有趣的。
Here's the new piece I wrote.
这是我写的新作品。
We're gonna come in hot
off the intro,
我们会热情地进来
关掉介绍，
so try to keep up.
所以尽量跟上。
Huh.
呵呵。
[guitar feedback]
[吉他反馈]
[heavy rock music]
[重摇滚]
♪ Ice cream, so tasty ♪
♪ 冰淇淋，太好吃了 ♪
♪ Freezing in my mouth ♪
♪ 在我嘴里冻结 ♪
♪ Icy pain inside my brain ♪
♪ 我的大脑冰冷的疼痛 ♪
♪ Won't you help me out? ♪
♪ 你不帮我吗？ ♪
♪ I have a brain freeze,
I have a brain freeze ♪
♪ 我的大脑冻结了，
我脑子有病了♪
♪ I have a brain freeze,
help me with my brain freeze ♪
♪ 我的大脑冻结了，
帮助我冻结我的大脑♪
♪ ♪
Can I have another sundae, please?
我可以再来一份圣代吗？
[crowd booing]
[人群嘘声]
They are not digging it, man.
他们没有挖它，伙计。
We told you guys to keep up.
我们告诉你们要跟上。
[mysterious tones]
[神秘的音调]
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
[laughs]
[笑]
Rock T. Puss, you came.
洛克·T·普斯，你来了。
Sorry I left you hanging, guys.
抱歉，我让你们悬着了，伙计们。
I did like being a bridge.
我确实喜欢成为一座桥梁。
But I was built to make music.
但我生来就是为了创作音乐的。
Say, how is the bridge?
话说，桥怎么样了？
Eh, I'm sure its fine.
嗯，我确定没问题。
[comical tones]
[滑稽的语气]
[panicked screams]
[惊慌的尖叫声]
Now, let's rock.
现在，让我们摇滚吧。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[crowd booing]
[人群嘘声]
The kids still don't like it.
What do we do?
孩子们还是不喜欢。
我们该怎么办？
Huh?
啊？
Maybe I can help with that.
也许我可以帮忙。
I'm DJ 2 Sc00pz,
我是 DJ 2 Sc00pz，
and I'm a huge
Goofy Scoopers fan.
我是一个巨大的
高飞独家粉丝。
Care to jam?
介意堵塞吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
both: Best
Goofy Scoopers show ever!
两者：最好
高飞独家表演！